Finding Aid for the The Francis Robinson Collection
Special Collections and University Archives
- (The File Description)
  - MET Opera House
    - Metropolitan Opera House - A Plan for the Future, Jan. 1977; Report to NY State Council of Arts, July 1977 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Performance Breakdowns (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Public Relations Program (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Personal Material
    - Correspondence (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - MET Building (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Kings College Chapel (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Resumes (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - DUPS (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Programs (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Robinson Negatives (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Photos (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Musical Autographs (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Magazine and Newspaper Clippings (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Magazine and Newspaper Clippings (Box 166, Folder 14)
  - Family Correspondence (Francis Robinson's Outgoing)
    - To Mother, early undated - pre Vanderbilt years (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - To Mother, early undated - Vanderbilt years (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - To Mother, early undated - Vanderbilt years (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - To Mother, early undated - Vanderbilt years (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - To Mother, working for Banner - WSM, undated (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - To Mother, 1927 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - To Mother, 9 Oct. 1929 - 1 Dec. 1931; undated fragments (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - To Mother, 23 Mar. 1932 - 24 Sep. 1934 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - To Mother, 8 Mar. 1935 - 1938; undated (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - To Mother, 17 Oct. 1938 - 27 Dec. 1939 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - To Mother, 9 Feb. 1940 - 19 Dec. 1941 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - To Mother, Jan. - 17 Dec. 1942 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - To Mother, 2 Jan. - 21 Dec. 1943; undated (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - To Mother, 2 Jan. - 25 Dec. 1944 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - To Mother, 6 Jan. 1945 - 4 Dec. 1946 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - To Mother, 1 Feb. 1947 - 28 Sep. 1948 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - To Mother, 4 Oct. 1948 - 30 Dec. 1949 (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - To Mother, 4 Feb. - 25 Dec. 1950 (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - To Mother, 3 Apr. 1951 - 22 Jul. 1952 (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - To Mother;23, Jul. 1952 - 14 Dec. 1953 (Box 167, Folder 20)
  - Family Correspondence (Francis Robinson's Outgoing)
    - To Mother, 15 Jan. - 25 Jun. 1954 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - To Mother, 12 Jul - 3 Dec. 1954 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - To Mother, 9 Jan. - 29 Jun. 1955 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - To Mother, 21 Jul - 31 Dec. 1955 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - To Mother, 24 Jan. - 29 Aug. 1956 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - To Mother, 30 Aug. - 28 Nov. 1956 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - To Mother, 7 Dec. 1956 - 20 May 1957 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - To Mother, 26 May - 25 Dec. 1957 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - To Mother, 6 Jan. - 27 Jun. 1958 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - To Mother, 6 Jul. - 20 Dec. 1958 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - To Mother, 4 Jan. - 9 Jul. 1959 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - To Mother, 18 Jul. - 29 Oct. 1959 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - To Mother, 5 Nov. 1959 - 25 May 1960 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - To Mother, 28 May, 1960 - 24 Mar. 1961 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - To Mother, 1 Apr. - 29 Sep. 1961 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - To Mother, 7 Oct. 1961 - 22 Apr. 1962 (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - To Mother, 27 Apr. - 28 Sep. 1962 (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - To Mother, 5 oct. 1962 - 30 Mar. 1963 (Box 168, Folder 18)
    - To Mother, 6 Apr. - 16 Jul. 1963 (Box 168, Folder 19)
    - To Mother, 22 Jul - 18 Oct. 1963 (Box 168, Folder 20)
    - To Mother, 26 Oct. 1963 - 25 Apr. 1964 (Box 168, Folder 21)
    - To Mother, 9 May - 7 Nov. 1964 (Box 168, Folder 22)
    - To Mother, 20 Nov. 1964 - 14 May 1965 (Box 168, Folder 23)
    - To Mother, 18 May - 18 Dec. 1965 (Box 168, Folder 24)
    - To Mother, 4 Feb. - 15 Jul. 1966 (Box 168, Folder 25)
    - To Mother, 5 Aug. - 30 Dec. 1966 (Box 168, Folder 26)
  - Family Correspondence (Francis Robinson's Outgoing)
    - To Mother, 5 Jan. - 31 Mar. 1967 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - To Mother, 7 Apr. - 26 Aug. 1967 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - To Mother, 1 Sep. - 29 Dec. 1967 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - To Mother, 12 Jan. - 21 Jun. 1968 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - To Mother, 25 Jul. - 6 Dec. 1968 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - To Mother, 9 Jan. - 29 May 1969 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - To Mother, 11 Jun. - 21 Nov. 1969 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - To Mother, 21 Nov. 1969 - 1 May 1970 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - To Mother, 15 May - 25 Aug. 1970 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - To Mother, 29 Aug. - 31 Dec. 1970 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - To Mother, 8 Jan. - 21 May 1971 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - To Mother, 28 May - 24 Sep. 1971 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - To Mother, 1 Oct. - 30 Dec. 1971 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - To Mother, 7 Jan. - 29 Jun. 1972 (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - To Mother, 3 Jul. - 29 Dec. 1972 (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - To Mother, 3 Jan. - 1 Jun. 1973 (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - To Mother, 8 Jun. - 28 Dec. 1973 (Box 169, Folder 17)
    - To Mother, 3 Jan. - 28 Jun. 1974 (Box 169, Folder 18)
    - To Mother, 4 Jul. - 27 Dec. 1974 (Box 169, Folder 19)
    - To Mother, 10 Jan. - 23 May, 1975 (Box 169, Folder 20)
    - To Mother, 30 May - 22 Nov. 1975 (Box 169, Folder 21)
    - To Mother, undated (Box 169, Folder 22)
    - undated fragments (1) (Box 169, Folder 23)
    - undated fragments (2) (Box 169, Folder 24)
    - undated fragments (3) (Box 169, Folder 25)
    - undated fragments (4) (Box 169, Folder 26)
  - Family Correspondence (Francis Robinson's Incoming)
    - A-C (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - D-F (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - G-I (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - J-L (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - M-P (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - R-Z (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Family Correspondence
    - Mrs. Francis Robinson to Mr. Francis Robinson, 1954 - 1975 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. Francis Robinson to Mr. Francis Robinson, undated (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. Francis Robinson to Mr. Francis Robinson, incomplete (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - To Mrs. Francis Robinson from others (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Margaret D. Akin to Mr. Francis Robinson (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Ratherine Arin to Mr. Francis Robinson (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Mr. Francis Robinson to His father (1 letter); To Mr. Francis Robinson from his relatives (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Misc. clippings and articles (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Ms. Geraldine Farrar to Mr. Francis Robinson)
    - 31 Dec. 1936 - 12 Jun. 1945 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - 27 Mar. 1945 - 9 Mar. 1951 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - 9 Dec. 1951 - 15 Oct. 1955 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - 5 Nov. 1956 - 31 Oct. 1958 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - 18 Nov. 1958 - 31 Aug., 1959 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - 14 Sep. 1959 - 28 May 1960 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - 3 Jun. 1960 - 15 Jan. 1961 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Jan. - May 1961 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Jun. - Dec. 1961 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Jan. - Dec. 1962 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Jan. - May 1963 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Jun. - Oct. 1963 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Nov. - Dec. 1963 (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Ms. Geraldine Farrar to Mr. Francis Robinson)
    - Jan. - May 1964 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Jun. - Oct. 1964 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Nov. 1964 - Mar. 1965 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Apr. - Jul. 1965 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Sep. - Dec. 1965 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Jan. - Apr. 1966 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - May - Jul. 1966 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence
    - Mrs. L. C. Naff to Mr. Francis Robinson, 1932 - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. L. C. Naff to Mr. Francis Robinson, 1943 - 1947 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. L. C. Naff to Mr. Francis Robinson, 1948 - 1949 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. L. C. Naff to Mr. Francis Robinson, 1950 - 1951 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. L. C. Naff to Mr. Francis Robinson, 1952 - 1955 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Mrs. L. C. Naff to Mr. Francis Robinson, 1956 -1960; undated (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Mr. Francis Robinson to Mrs. L. C. Naff, 1938 - 1939 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Mr. Francis Robinson to Mrs. L. C. Naff, 1940 - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Mr. Francis Robinson to Mrs. L. C. Naff, 1942 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Mr. Francis Robinson to Mrs. L. C. Naff, 1943 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Mr. Francis Robinson to Mrs. L. C. Naff, 1944 - 1949 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Mr. Francis Robinson to Mrs. L. C. Naff, 1950 - 1960 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Mrs. L. C. Naff to others (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Mrs. L. C. Naff to others (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Others to Mrs. L. C. Naff (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Others to Mrs. L. C. Naff (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Others to Mrs. L. C. Naff (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (Mr. Francis Robinson and Ms. Geraldine Farrar)
    - "This is your life", Correspondence 1955 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Featured Articles (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Retirement (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Collection to Nashville Public Library (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Clippings (dated and undated, including her death Sep. 1955) (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Clippings (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Clippings (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Clippings (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 1966 - 1967 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - Autographs Acquired Correspondence
    - Autographs (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Autograph Facsimles (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Calve - Galli Curci (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Garden, M. 1921 - 1930 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Garden, M. 1931 - 1935 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Garden, M. 1937 - 1949; undated (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Gatti - Casazzo (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Gigli - Pinza (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Pons - Toscanini (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Melba, Patti, Walter II (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence and Photographs (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Performing Arts Center (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - General (Francis Robinson) (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Francis Robinson's Lectures
    - Robinson Lecture Announcements - undated, 1954-1969 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Robinson Lecture Announcements - 1970-1974 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Robinson the Lecturer - FR Material (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Lecture Contracts (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Robinson as a Performer (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Robinson - Biographical Material (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Articles by Francis Robinson
    - "Caruso: A Legendary Performer" (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Oversize Notes (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - "Gala in Atlanta", Town and Country, May 1955 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - "The Season: New York", Town and Country, Nov. 1955 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - "Happy Birthday, General Marshall", Town and Country, Dec. 1955 "Happy Birthday, General Marshall! Anniversary Recalls Wartime Visit", The Times-Picayune, Dec. 31, 1955 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - "Caruso", Town and Country, Mar. 1956 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - "Metropolitan Opera Tours America", Town and Country, Apr. 1957 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - "Caruso's Naples", Town and Country, Oct. 1957 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - "Renata Tebaldi: Portrait of a Model Prima Donna", High Fidelity, Nov. 1957 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - "Of Orfeo and Rise Stevens", Town and Country, Jan. 1958 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - "Beauty in Sound and Form", Town and Country, Oct. 1959 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - "Singing for High Stakes", Town and Country, Nov. 1959 (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - Articles by Francis Robinson
    - "Festive Opera Benefit", Town and Country, Mar. 1961 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - "Gerry's Forty Years Later", Metropolitan Opera, 1961-1962 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - "The Leningrad Tradition", Town and Country, Sep. 1961 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - "Beautiful Voices to Spend the Summer With", Vogue, Jul. 1962 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - "Puccini's First Turandot", Metropolitan Opera, 1963-1964 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - "Munich Gateway", Town and Country, Nov. 1963 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - "Nuremberg's Magic Restoration', Town and Country, Dec. 1963 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - "Olympics at Innsbruck", Town and Country, Jan. 1964 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - "Galli-Curici: Memoir of a Beloved and Dazzling Artist", Show, Apr. 1964 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - "Opera Across the U.S.A.", Harper's Bazaar, Aug. 1967 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Articles by Francis Robinson
    - Articles on Banner (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - WSM Radio Scripts, Late Season 1937-1938 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Drafts, Ontlines - Speeches, Articles, Press Releases (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Opera News (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Notes, Speeches, Articles, etc. (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Drafts, Outlines - Speeches,, Articles, Press Releases (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Personal Material
    - Mt. Pleasant Student (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Mt. Pleasant and Area Material (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Family Members; Robinson Coat of Arms (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Dr. Herbert Sanborn (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - James G. Stahlman (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - By or about Nashville Area People; Robinson in Nashville Activities (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Theatre Press Agent (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Service Records - Navy, Vaval Reserve, Veteran's (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - The New School (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Obits, Verdi Reguiem Memorial (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Personal Material - Notes, Worksheets, Original Catalogs
    - Singers (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Pianists (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Enrico Caruso Jr (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Celebration (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Work Sheets (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Catalog (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Catalog (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Personal Material
    - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings (about FR) (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, Booklets (about FR) (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Votes of Confidence (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Materials (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Materials (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Materials (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Personal and Biographical Material (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Personal Material
    - Photograph (Mr. Francis Robinson and Ms. Katherine Aldin) (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Leveridge, Mr. 1744 Benifit Ticket (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Certificate - Doctor of Letters to Francis Robinson, Westminster Choir College, Princeton, New Jersey (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Personal Material
    - Programs; Magazine and Newspaper Clippings (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Programs; Magazine and Newspaper Clippings (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Photos (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Photos (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - FR's Article Manuscripts (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Operas (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - MET Programs (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - McCormack, Wilbur (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - Personal Material
    - A gift (a penguin toy) from the staff and manager of the MET Opera Club (Box 187)
  - Robinson and Vanderbilt
    - Activities at Vanderbilt (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Papers (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Thesis (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - 1934 - Rhodes Scholar Candidate (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Guest Lecturer at Vanderbilt (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Vanderbilt Alumni and Board of Trust (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Collection Gift to VUL (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Vanderbilt Alumnus (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Vanderbilt Publications (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - People Associated with Vanderbilt (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Organizations
    - AFTRA (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Association of Theatrical Press Agents and Managers (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - The Bagby Foundation for the Musical Arts, Inc. (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - National Press Club (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Coffee House (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Dutch Treat Club (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Italian Folklore Society (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - The Kentuckians (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Cambs (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Lotus Club (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - The Players (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - The Tennessee Society in New York (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - The Ziegfield Club (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Certificates, Awards and Honors (Box 189, Folder 14)
  - Churches & Religious Services
    - Churches (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Churches (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Churches (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Invitations
  - Postcards
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings
    - Journals - Formes et Couleurs (Paris) (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Journals - L'illustration (Paris) (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Journals - Book of New York (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Journals - Vogue (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - A folder - Puccini: La Boheme (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings
    - Misc. materials (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Life - series on the History of Western Culture (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Egypt (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Places - general (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - England (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Germany & Austria (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Greece (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Israel (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Italy (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Mexico (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - New York (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Russia (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Scandinavia (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - U.S.A. (Box 194, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings
    - Temples - Greece (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Bernini (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Brague (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Burchfield, Charles (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Chinese Art (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Dali, Salvador (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Cocteau, Jean (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - De Vinci, Leonardo (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - De Chirico, Giorgio (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Degas, Edgar (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Duty, Raoul (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Durer, Albrecht (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Egyptian Art (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Goya (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - El Gruo (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Greek Art (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - Avery Handly, Jr. (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Edward Hicks (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - William Hogarth (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - Edward Hopper (Box 195, Folder 19)
    - Tournse Lantree (Box 195, Folder 20)
    - Edy Legrand (Box 195, Folder 21)
    - Henri Matisse (Box 195, Folder 22)
    - Michelangelo (Box 195, Folder 23)
    - Grandona Moses (Box 195, Folder 24)
    - Picasso (Box 195, Folder 25)
    - John Piper (Box 195, Folder 26)
    - Rambramdt (Box 195, Folder 27)
    - Vincent Vangogh (Box 195, Folder 28)
    - James McNeill Whister (Box 195, Folder 29)
    - Multiple Artists (Box 195, Folder 30)
    - Art - Architects Cippings (Box 195, Folder 31)
    - Gertrude Stein, Art Patron (Box 195, Folder 32)
    - Louvre (Box 195, Folder 33)
    - Portrais; Portraitists (Box 195, Folder 34)
    - Art - Photography Clippings (Box 195, Folder 35)
    - Art - General Clippings (Box 195, Folder 36)
    - Art Exhibition Catalogues; Announcements (Box 195, Folder 37)
    - Architecture - Cathedrals - England (Box 195, Folder 38)
    - Churches and Cathedrals - France (Box 195, Folder 39)
    - Cathedrals - Germany, Austria (Box 195, Folder 40)
    - Churches and Cathedrals - Italy (Box 195, Folder 41)
    - Churches and Cathedrals - Spain (Box 195, Folder 42)
    - Churches and Cathedrals - USA (Box 195, Folder 43)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings
    - Country Music (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Music (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Music (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Music (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Violins (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Pianos (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings
    - Art/Film (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Arts & Culture (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Art (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Art (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings - Public Figures
    - Public Figures (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Thomas Deway (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Albert Einstein (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Dwight D. Eisenhower (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Gerald Ford (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Andrew Jackson (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Thomas Jefferson (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Hellen Keller (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Charles A. Lindburgh (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - John Lindsay (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Golda Meir (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Earl Mountbatten (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - William S. Paley (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Political Figures (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - John D. Rockefeller HI (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - The Rothschild Family (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - Albert Schweitzer (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - Sports Personalities (Box 198, Folder 19)
    - Harry S. Truman (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - Joseph Urban (Box 198, Folder 21)
    - Duke of Windsor (Box 198, Folder 22)
    - Frances Wolcott (Box 198, Folder 23)
  - Enrico Caruso
    - Publicity Material, 1902-03, 1918-19 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Others on Caruso (contemporary accounts, reminiscences) (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Caricatures by Caruso (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Programs of Caruso's Performance in Russia (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Programs and Booklets, 1904-1918 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Programs and BoOklets, 1904-1918 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Enrico Caruso
    - Scrapbook (1) (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (2) (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Copies of News and Articles, 18954908 (for FR's research on Caruso) (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Copies of News, Articles, 1909-1928, undated (for FR's research on Caruso) (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - "Caruso" Programs, Broadcast Clippings (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Caruso's Checkbook (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Copies of Programs and Announcements/Photos (Transactions from 2 Oct. 1918 through 28 May 1921) (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Cover Sheets of the Magazines (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Enrico Caruso
    - Memorabilia (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Victor Record Booklets, 1905-1930 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Religious Services in Memory of Caruso (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Portions of Enrico Caruso: His Life and Death by Dorothy Caruso (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Caruso's Family (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Program in Memory of Caruso (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - "A Century of Caruso" - A Special Issue of Opera News (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Items (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Magazines and Newspapers - with texts by FR (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Caruso's Recordings (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Enrico Caruso
    - Zirato, Bruno - Correspondence, Astruc - Franklin (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Zirato, Bruno - Correspondence, Fujita - Kahrs (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Zirato, Bruno - Correspondence, Kahrs - Puccini (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Zirato, Bruno - Correspondence, Reynolds - Ybarra (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Caruso Documentaries, Apr. 27, 1959 - Jan. 19, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Caruso Family Correspondence, Jan. 1919 - Nov. 1957 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Caruso Correspondence, Jul. 1918 - Jun. 1920 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - FR's Book Contracts (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Caruso Unidentified Correspondence (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Enrico Caruso
    - Caruso - Clippings, 1922-1953 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Caruso - Clippings, 1954-1959 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Caruso - Clippings, 1960-1971 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Caruso - Clippings, 1972-1978 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Caruso - Clippings, 1922-1953 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Caruso - Clippings, undated (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Caruso - Seemungal's Research (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Caruso - Studies of Voice, Sound Production, Medical Condition (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Caruso - Catalogues of Caruso's Book Collection (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Caruso - Performance Records (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Caruso - Audio Recording Records (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Caruso - Library and Museum Holdings of Caruso Material (Box 203, Folder 12)